ADAM TAN KHEE HAN

Games Programmer

LinkedIn | Github | Portfolio

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Worked as a Junior Games Programmer and created multiple Gameplay Systems for our Multiplayer Games made in Unreal Engine 5. Developed an understanding of Unreal's Gameplay Ability System and Multiplayer and Networking. Loves to solve problems. Always open to suggestions and ideas to write more efficient code.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Languages: C++, C#

Software Experience: JetBrains Rider, Visual Studio, Unreal Engine, Unity, Git BASH, GitHub, Sourcetree

Gameplay Programming: Implementations of complex Multiplayer Gameplay System logic using Blueprints and C++, and the Gameplay Ability System, ensuring efficient replication and accurate to desired design

Other: Experience with working on teams of up to 6, Programmers and Artists, on our current project. Helping each other solve complex gameplay issues

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

PSYCHOHOUND LTD THIRSK, UK

Junior Games Programmer

SEP 2022-AUG2023

- Projects: Ruff 'N' Tumble, AUDL, From Beyond
- Built Multiplayer Ready Gameplay Systems using Unreal Engine 5 with Blueprints and C++
- Built UI according to design using Unreal Motion Graphics (UMG)
- Utilized Gameplay Ability System for complex Gameplay Mechanics
- Produced efficient code where possible to ensure smooth gameplay and prevent hitches
- Worked closely with other Programmers, Artists, and Designers to ensure desired results
- Managed source control for our projects and to ensure all conflicts are resolved correctly

ADDITIONAL WORK EXPERIENCE

LEMONGRASS	Redcar, UK
Waiter	JULY 2022 – AUG 2022
Coco & Rum	Saltburn, UK
Waiter	JULY 2021 – JAN 2022
ZOEWEBS	Penang, Malaysia
Website Developer Intern	DEC 2018 – MAY 2019

EDUCATION

TEESSIDE UNIVERSITY

BSc (Hons) Computer Games Programming (2:1)

MIDDLESBROUGH, UK

SEP 2019 – MAY 2021

KDU PENANG COLLEGE UNIVERSITY

Diploma in Games Technology (CGPA 3.38)

PENANG, MALAYSIA APR 2017 – APR 2019

PROJECTS

ASTRONAUGHT EPIC MEGAJAM 2023

Games Programmer

Unreal Engine 5, C++

14 SEP 23 - 21 SEP 23

- Exploration Tower Defense Game with the objective of escaping the planet by fighting and gathering resources on a hostile planet
- Made Gameplay Systems such as Resource and Building spawning
- Worked in a team of 5 to create a game for the Epic MegaJam

HOBBIES & INTEREST

Gaming: Have a passion for gaming. Some of my all-time favourites are The Legend of Zelda series (especially Sprit Tracks and Phantom Hourglass), Shin Megami Tensei: Persona series and Kingdom Hearts series.

FPS Games: Enjoy playing FPS games since young, my favourites are Team Fortress 2 and Half Life Series. I also played a lot of Rainbow Six Siege and Counter Strike

Puzzle Games: Love puzzle games like The Room series and Portal series especially the co-op

Baking & Cooking: Enjoy making food and baked goods for friends. I find the process fun and calming. I have a keen interest in baking bread (especially sourdough)

LANGUAGES

English (Native); Malay (Bilingual); Mandarin (Basic); Japanese (Basic)